Ter Guohao

Contact Number: +65 9663 3976 Email: terguohao@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Aims to make a difference by creating value for stakeholders and society through innovation, critical analysis and feasibility testing. Enjoys meeting new people and sharing of ideas and experiences. Currently working towards CPA and CFA Level I

EXPERIENCE

Ardent Associates LLP

Feb 2016 to present

Audit Associate

- Performed statutory audit of private limited companies (extensive experience in funds and asset management companies)
- Participated in audit engagements with large group of companies and conglomerates
- Ensure funds and asset management companies comply with Securities and Futures Act, in accordance to Monetary Authority of Singapore regulations
- Analysis of business models and financial performance with application of key financial ratios
- Conducted internal audits on behalf of ministries

Partners Group (Singapore) Pte. Ltd.

Sept 2015 to Dec 2015

Financial analyst / Fund accountant

- Management of 6 to 8 funds to prepare financial reports in accordance to IFRS or US GAAP
- Performed net asset finalization, which includes portfolio valuation analysis, hedging and stock valuation
- Review of monthly revaluation of financial asset investments (private equity, real estate, infrastructure etc)
- Ensure compliance with company's internal procedures and processes
- Liaising with external and internal auditors

Lo Hock Ling & Co.

March 2013 to Feb 2015

Audit Associate

- Involved in statutory audit of private limited companies from various industries (trading companies, general retailers, clubs and associations, investment-holding companies etc)
- Participated in audit engagements in the process of audit planning, fieldwork and audit finalisation
- Audit of financial statements in accordance with Singapore Financial Reporting Standards
- Performed testing and reviews of internal controls and processes to ensure compliance with generally accepted accounting principles

Ter Guohao

Contact Number: +65 9663 3976 Email: terguohao@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Royal Melbourne Institute of Technology

- Singapore Institute of Management

2010 to 2013

BBACC - Bachelor of Business (Accountancy)

- Achieved High Distinctions in *Ethics, Micro-Econs, Macro-Econs, Introductory Accounting*.
- Awarded top scorer award in *Ethical Issues in Accountancy*.

Nanyang Polytechnic

2004 to 2007

Diploma in nursing

Junyuan Secondary School

2000 to 2003

5 GCE 'O' Levels credits, scored B3 in English

PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATIONS

- ➤ ISCA PE candidate, *previously known as CPA SG* (completed in June 2015)
- ➤ Microsoft Office (Word, Powerpoint, Excel)

CCA

SIM Dragonboat Club – Member

Achievements

- April 2013 NTUC Income Run350 21km Half Marathon
- Dec 2010 Standard Chartered 42.195 km Marathon

National Service 2007 to 2009

Medic Sergeant at SAFTI Military Institute

- Led team of medics to Brunei, Taiwan, Thailand to cover safety for OCS training troops
- Received commendation for saving an Officer Cadet during Taiwan exercise

Ter Guohao

Contact Number: +65 9663 3976 Email: terguohao@gmail.com